YYeTs.com
人人影视
*Better pray for hell*
时间轴： 浓子   萌    校对： 苏小黛   胖兔纯
Burn in hell!
烧死在地狱里
Sin!
罪恶
Be assured, Mrs. Bridget --
放心  布里奇特小姐
ones that are weepin'
为你哭泣之人
far outnumber the ones that might spit or curse.
远比唾弃诅咒之人多
Burn in hell! Burn!
烧死在地狱里  烧吧
You would do well to pay that boy extra
多给那人点钱让他把尸体
to take them bodies a more circuitous route.
送去更远的地方就更好了
Spectacle is fuel for our fire.
人们的围观是我们烈火的燃料
And doubt is indulged by the rich and spoiled only.
质疑可是富人和受宠者的特权
Mind that you was born neither.
记住  你以前可既不富有  也没人宠溺
"Give me to die with thee that I may rise to a new life,
让我与你一同死去吧  而后我将重生
"for I wish to be as dead and buried to sin,
我希望自己的罪恶和自私  都被
to selfishness..."
长埋地下...
By all means, Reverend...
辛苦了  牧师
Do not offer prayer or comfort or words of encouragement.
千万别说任何祈祷安慰或者鼓励的话
No, stand as a bewildered statue
对  就这样如一座不知所措的雕像般
amongst the people of Salem
站在塞勒姆的人民中间
and offer them absolutely nothing.
什么都不说  什么都不做
What would you have me do?
那您想让我怎么做
What I brought you here to do.
我让你来是干什么的
Guide and support us in our great hour of need.
在我们需要指引时帮助我们啊
Warm our hearts with your words of wisdom.
用你充满智慧的言辞温暖我们的心灵
Assure us it is God's will we do in ferreting out the devil.
让大家知道除掉恶魔是上帝的旨意
Or at the very, very least...
或者至少...
Pray.
祈祷吧
Tragic day.
悲惨的一天啊
Tragic but necessary.
虽然悲惨  但有必要
Tragically necessary.
很遗憾这是必要的
Surely, the grieving of the masses gives you pause.
众人的哀悼可以让你暂时歇口气了吧
Most spit and curse
大多数人唾弃诅咒她
while summoning the burning flames of hell.
同时还召唤地狱之火的焚烧
There are also
也有人
those who weep for her and find her hanging unfounded.
为她哭泣  觉得绞死她毫无根据
Not enough to divert our intentions.
区区几个人  不足为意
A panic's success relies on its escalation.
要让众人的恐慌不断加剧才算成功
The grand rite has begun.
大祭典已经开始
We look to our next victim.
我们需要寻找下一个受害者
And that I disagree,
我的一切反对
that I strenuously and most vehemently oppose
如此强烈表示出我的不赞同
means nothing to you?
对你毫无意义可言吗
We were seen at our sabbat.
我们祭祀时被人看见了
And you throw caution to the wind.
你竟然还这么公然行事
And have you identified who saw us?
那你查出看见我们的人了吗
Perhaps your disagreements and vehement opposition
如果你能完成这点简单的任务
might hold more weight if you could be relied on
或许你的不同意见和强烈反对
to complete a simple task.
能多一些分量
Good day, Hale.
祝你今天愉快  霍尔
What must I do to be saved?
我要怎么做才能得到救赎
It is impossible to ask a more weighty question.
没有比这更重要的问题了
Lest we perish eternally.
恐怕我们都将永恒逝去
How's it feel?
感觉如何
How does what feel?
什么感觉如何
Killing two innocents in as many days.
两天之内杀死两个无辜之人
- The evidence against Miss Bishop. - The orphanage!
-证据指向毕谢普小姐  -孤儿院出事了
Help! They're looting the orphanage!
来人啊  他们在洗劫孤儿院
Get out!
出去
It's not yours!
这不是你的
Get...
滚...
Next one's to your head.
下一枪就是你的脑袋了
Are you okay?
你还好吗
It's awful. It's too awful.
太可怕了  太可怕了
W-what's happened?
出什么事了
Thieves have come to ransack the orphanage
盗贼们来抢劫孤儿院
now that the town sees fit to hang its guardian.
把这儿的守护者绞死  如今大家尝到滋味了吧
Easy, son.
冷静点  孩子
This is what comes of your witch panic.
这都是巫师恐慌造成的
Are you all right?
你还好吗
This is your fault! And his.
这都是你的错  还有他
Forgive her. She's distraught.
原谅她  她受惊了
I'm right!
我没说错
See me home.
送我回家
Captain, if you wouldn't mind, hmm?
上尉  如果你不介意
Yes. Of course.
当然可以
Where have they taken her?
他们把她带去哪里了
Foul spot where they rest the unwanted.
埋葬被遗弃者的污秽之所
Is it very terrible?
很糟糕吗
Yes.
是的
Thank you...
谢谢你
for your heroism and your candor.
感谢你的勇敢与坦诚
Welcome, welcome, welcome!
欢迎  欢迎  欢迎
A cup of tea?
来杯茶吗
-A touch of port? -No time.
-来口波特酒  -没空
Who saw us in the woods?
在树林看见我们的是谁
It was...he who is marked.
是拥有烙印之人
He of the "F" that furrows his brow.
他的眉上烙着"F"
-Issac? -The fornicator.
-艾萨克  -私通者
The idiot.
那个蠢货
One more thing.
还有一件事
Isaac was not alone.
艾萨克并非独自一人
Who else was with him?
还有谁跟他一起
I don't know.
我不知道
I could not make out the face.
我看不清那张脸
You don't know.
你不知道
What good are you?
你有何用
A seer who can't see.
看不见的鬼眼
It's not an exact art.
我的法术并不精确
Evidently not.
看出来了
Hello?
有人吗
What the hell was that place?
那是什么鬼地方
The shack belongs to Petrus,
彼得鲁斯的窝棚
an expert on creatures both feral and otherwise.
他是野生及驯养动物的专家
Yeah, well, they looked dead...until they didn't.
它们看起来是死的  但却不是
No, dead animal
死去的动物
could threaten a storied soldier such as yourself, captain.
可伤不到像你这样的老兵  上尉
It could, if powered by forces we don't understand.
要是被施了什么未知的法术  就有可能了
-Such as? -Witchcraft.
-比如  -巫术
-Nonsense. -Is it?
-胡说  -是吗
You know him well, this Petrus?
你很了解他吗  这个彼得鲁斯
You'll find no man more ordinary than Petrus.
没有比彼得鲁斯更普通的人了
To say that he's mundane is to overstate his passion.
说他平凡都高估他的激情了
And what ordinary task brought you deep into the forest
那是什么普通的任务让你来到森林深处
to seek his mundane counsel?
寻求他平凡的建议
Easy, son...
别激动  孩子
Or I might suspect your presence here
不然我可能都要怀疑
as more than a coincidence,
你的出现也并非偶然了
That, perhaps, for reasons of your own
也许你有你的理由
about which I'm sure you'd rather I not inquire,
我相信你不希望我问起
you might have followed me here.
你怕是跟踪我来此的吧
And what a shame...
你对小女这般仁慈
to have suspicion overtake the grace I owe
我却让怀疑之心遮蔽了感激之意
for the kindness you showed my daughter.
真是令人遗憾
Consider it repaid.
就算是扯平了吧
Right.
也好
George, really.
乔治  不是吧
You are worse than a child.
你连个孩子都不如
He serves at my behest, not yours.
它听从我的吩咐  不听你的
He won't come out for you.
你是没法让它出来的
There, there, little man.
安静点  小家伙
Oh, pay the beast no mind.
不用理会这个老怪物
Rest now, and I'll see to your feeding later.
先歇息  稍后我再来喂你
Isaac's brung the master's potions.
艾萨克把先生的药剂拿来了
Tell him to wait.
让他等等
Ohh, George.
乔治
Your nightdress thoroughly drenched in sick.
你的睡衣都被呕吐物彻底弄脏了
Stew in that for the day, my sweet.
今天就穿着它吧  亲爱的
For Mr. Sibley.
给西布里先生的
Oh, and not a moment too soon.
你要是早点来就好了
Just now, he suffered a fit of sorts.
他现在状态不太好
If you don't mind me saying so, ma'am,
如果您不介意的话  夫人
It's a burden you've took on...
我想说这真是您一直承受着的重担
A burden and load, carried out without cry or complaint.
一份不能言说  只能独自承受的重荷
My burdens can't compare to that of salem itself.
我的担子跟塞勒姆的没法比
How do you find the spirits on the square?
广场上的气氛如今怎么样了
Low, ma'am. Awful low.
消沉  夫人  非常消沉
Perhaps there is solace to be found
或许这么想能聊以慰藉
in remembrance of times when we've both shouldered worse.
毕竟我们都曾承受过更糟的状况
Who could have imagined that a single night
谁能想到仅仅一晚
could have consequence for so many?
影响会如此之大呢
Not all scars can be seen.
不是所有的伤疤都能被看到
But they exist nonetheless.
但它们却切实存在着
Next morning, she was gone.
第二天一早  她走了
Run away and disappeared.
逃离了这里  就这么消失了
Oh, your sweet abby.
你心爱的艾比
I'll admit to wondering on occasion
我得承认  有时候会想
What it might be like to one day see her again
如果有天能再见到她会是什么样
Or know of her or hear her fate.
会想  如果听说了她的境况
Would it be better or so much worse?
会是好事还是更糟呢
I can assure you, Isaac...
我向你保证  艾萨克
If you were to see her again,
如果你还能再见到她
you would find those feelings buried too deeply
你会发现那些感觉被埋葬得太深
for hope of resurrection.
已然无法复燃了
Good afternoon, Isaac.
再见  艾萨克
G'day, ma'am.
告辞  夫人
What is that?
那是什么
What is that? What are you... what are you doing?
那是什么  你要干什么
Please. Please.
别  求你
What did you see in the woods?
你在树林里看到了什么
We knew you weren't alone.
我们知道你不是只身一人
We know!
我们知道
We know! We know!
我们知道  我们知道
Who was there?! Who was there?!
还有谁在  还有谁在
I was alone!
只有我一个人
Get it all.
弄干净了
Want no trace of our efforts.
千万别留下线索
The fault must lie with him alone.
要查也只能查到他一个人
And put these in his pockets.
把这些放进他口袋
If he's to be found a witch,
如果要指证他是巫师
The good reverend will require proof...
那牧师一定会需要证据
...evidence to seal his fate, hmm?
决定他命运的证据  懂吗
What is it?
怎么了
Is this sympathy that I'm sensing?
我看到的是同情吗
One outcast to the other?
一个流浪汉对另一个流浪汉的同情
Is that what you feel, you decrepit deformity?
你是这么想的吗  老怪物
Mary!
玛丽
So now even you would question me?
现在连你都敢质疑我了
Do as you're told!
照我说的做
Does your great Mary know what it is to watch witches burn?
你伟大的玛丽知道眼看着女巫们被烧死是什么感觉吗
Nothing of the old ways
她对传统一屑不顾
while she's whipping us toward the new.
只顾着鞭策我们向新的方向前进
A spell of vitae cupido,
给他下个疯狂咒
And then we send him to the one place in town
然后将他送去镇上
That will certainly deny him entrance.
他绝对不允许进入的地方
That should get their attention.
应该会引起他们的注意
You're crying.
你哭了
I'm not.
没有
You are.
你就是在哭
What's wrong?
怎么了
If they can hang a woman like miss Bishop,
他们连毕谢普小姐那样的人都要绞死
What does that mean for someone like me?
那我这样的人怎么办
Nothing is going to happen to you.
你不会有事的
How can you be so sure?
你怎么知道
Just yesterday, it was me that they put before the Lewis girl.
昨天他们还把我推到那个路易斯面前呢
Would you have come forward had I been accused?
如果我被指控  你会站出来吗
I follow every protocol.
我做的一切都严守程序
I adhere to every letter of what my father taught me.
我遵从父亲教给我的每一个字
No one is convicted without incontrovertible evidence.
没有人会被定罪  除非有无可争议的证据
So you're certain miss Bishop was a witch?
所以你确信毕谢普小姐是个女巫
I am certain...
我确信..
of the evidence.
那些证据
Why do you do it?
你为什么那么做
Why?
为什么
Is it that you believe that you're doing good?
你相信你是在做好事吗
Or is it that you wish to please your father?
还是你只想取悦你的父亲
It's Isaac! He's mad!
是艾萨克  他疯了
I can't be seen here.
不能让人看见我在这儿
Let me touch you!
来让我摸摸
Get up!
起来
Isaac, no!
艾萨克  不要
Isaac, what are you doing?
艾萨克  你在干什么
What do you see?!
你看到了什么
Isaac!
艾萨克
Oh there you are!
你终于来了
Isaac the fornicator! Isaac the fornicator!
私通者艾萨克  私通者艾萨克
Hide your wives! Hide all your sheep!
藏好你们的老婆  藏好你们的羊
Isaac the fornicator will get them when they sleep!
私通者艾萨克会在他们睡觉时发动袭击
Isaac the fornicator!
私通者艾萨克
Hide your wives! Hide your wives!
藏好你们的老婆  藏好你们的老婆
Hide all your sheep!
藏好你们的羊
Isaac the fornicator! Hide your wives!
私通者艾萨克  藏好你们的老婆
- Isaac!  - Hide your sheep. Isaac the fornicator.
-艾萨克  -藏好你们的羊  私通者艾萨克
Stop! Isaac!
停下  艾萨克
Jonathan, it's no good. It's no good!
约翰森  大事不妙  大事不妙
What is no good?
什么不妙
They saw us. They saw us.
他们看到我们了  他们看到我们了
They saw us in the woods.
他们看到我们在树林里
They saw us.
他们看到我们了
They saw us in the woods. They saw us.
他们看到我们在树林里  他们看到我们了
Shut up.
闭嘴
Take him to the jail.
把他送进监狱
They saw us in the woods.
他们看到我们在树林里
They saw us.
他们看到我们了
Magistrate.
治安官
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
What have you done?
你都干了什么
The idiot saw us in the woods.
那个白痴看到了我们在树林里
Isaac.
艾萨克
So, you did this without consent?
所以你未经我允许就动手了
He wasn't alone.
他不是一个人
We'll find out who was with him, and he will burn.
我们会找出和他一起的人  他会被烧死
No, you will do nothing further.
不  你什么都别想做
- But... - Nothing!
-但是  -别想了
Go home, magistrate.
回家去  治安官
You reek of the woods.
你身上有股森林的臭气
Find me Rose.
把萝丝找来
A drunken romp, that's all --
醉鬼撒酒疯  仅此而已
A young man's prerogative.
年轻人的特权
And yet no smell of spirits on him.
但他身上根本没有酒味
Oh, well, burn him, then. Why wait?
那就烧了他  还等什么
If he was spelled, he's blameless in his actions.
如果他被下咒了就不该为自己的行为受罚
Yet you still hold him. Why?
那你为什么还关着他
Found on his person.
在他身上找到的
Likely stolen to cast a spell on its owner.
很可能是偷来对物品的主人下咒的
One minute, he's speller.
前一分钟他是下咒者
The next, he's bewitched.
下一分钟就成了受害者
Make up your mind, reverend.
拿个主意吧  牧师
Is he a witch or a victim of the craft?
他究竟是巫师还是巫术的受害者
Chief ingredient of a witch's brew.
巫师炼药的主要成分
Isaac took me into those woods.
艾萨克带我进入那片树林
He risked his life to show me the witches.
他冒着生命危险带我去看那些巫师
Why, if he was one?
如果他是其中一员为什么要这么做
I've, uh, administrated a tonic
我给他灌了点
that'll settle him down and, uh, end the fits.
能让他安静下来  不再发狂的药剂
What is your surgeon's opinion of the boy's condition?
以你作为医师的判断  你怎么看
I can't say for sure as to cause or source,
我不能确定病因
but going by his babble,
但从他胡言乱语的状况看
that boy is good and touched.
那个孩子估计是精神失常了
Every benefit of the doubt,
我们要尽可能相信他
every avenue explored.
找出所有可能的原因
The boy is one of our own.
那个孩子是我们中的一员
Outcast and shunned as he may be,
尽管他不被人们接受  遭受唾弃
he still resides in the bosom of Salem.
但他依然生活在塞勒姆
I'll, uh --
我会
I'll speak with him personally.
我会和他单独聊聊
Not tonight, you won't.
今晚不行
And why not?
为什么
Lamb gave Isaac a tonic to help him sleep.
兰姆给艾萨克服食了一些助于入睡的药剂
Probably best, magistrate, to return in the morning.
我想您最好早上再来  治安官
Yes, magistrate.
是的  治安官
You can have your personal talk with him then.
到时候你可以和他单独聊聊
Rose, absent the magistrate,
萝丝  抛开治安官不谈
what chance have I of harnessing the body's allegiance?
我有多大机会得到大家的忠诚
The others are split between old and new.
旧派与新派的支持者各有千秋
Difficult to predict the outcome of such a divide.
很难说这种分歧会带来什么结果
You're old
你年岁不轻
and yet somehow not governed by this fear.
却没有被这种恐惧所支配
It is not age that divides us, but ambition.
区分我们的不是年龄  而是野心
Well, he's not without ambition.
他并非没有野心
It chafes him to bend to a woman,
屈从于女人让他愤懑
but he does so that our greater purpose may live.
他之所以仍这么做是为了我们的大义
It was to be me that led us.
我们说好了的  由我带领大家
It was and it is.
没错  如今也依然如此
Questioned and challenged at every turn,
但如今我的权威却总受到质问及挑战
each and every decision soliciting doubt and scrutiny.
每一项决定都会受到怀疑和监视
Much as we may wish it,
我们再如何渴望
primacy does not live in the abyss.
深渊中也不存在权力
It cannot have all been in vain.
一切牺牲绝不能白费
Sibley.
西布里
Your baby.
你的孩子
It cannot have all been in vain.
一切牺牲绝不能白费
This life, my...
这种生活  我的
Choices.
你的选择
Was there a choice?
有选择吗
Or was choice taken from me?
还是我选择的权力早已被剥夺
It's too late now to think of such things.
现在想这些事为时已晚
Is it?
是吗
It mustn't have been easy seeing him again.
再次见到他肯定不容易
It is yours to decide, my girl,
决定权在你  孩子
what is in vain and what is not.
这些牺牲会不会白费
And you will stand behind my decision?
你会支持我的决定吗
Up to a point.
我会有限度地支持
The magister's roots are old.
主人的根基很深
He has seen much and suffered greatly.
他见识过许多也经受了很多痛苦
Do not underestimate him.
不要低估他
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
Captain Alden.
奥登上尉
Isaac is not a witch.
艾萨克不是巫师
You do nothing, he'll be hung for one.
你什么都不做的话他就会被绞死
We have to stop this.
我们得制止这件事
There's nothing left in you.
如今的你陡剩一副躯壳
No feelings, no heart.
没有情感  没有恻隐之心
You're not the girl I once knew.
你不再是我曾经认识的那个女孩了
Have they questioned him?
他们审问过他了吗
No.
还没有
That's because he was given a sleeping tonic.
因为医师给他喝了安眠药剂
So he's said nothing.
所以他什么都没说
Nothing.
没说
But Cotton is eager,
但是柯顿
and the magistrate was hard to turn away.
以及治安官都早已迫不及待
Hale? Was there?
霍尔  他也在吗
He came straight to question him.
他就是去审问他的
You have my complete allegiance.
相信我  我一定会站在你这边
"Our opportunities to do good are our talents."
"行善举之机会即是我等之天资"
My father said that.
这是我父亲说的
The great Increase Mather.
伟大的英克里斯·麦哲
To stay impartial, to weigh without bias --
不偏不倚  公正无私
is this the good I am meant to do?
这就是我该做的善举吗
I don't want your life in my hands.
我不想让你了断在我手里
Half of Salem takes you for a fool.
塞勒姆一半的人觉得你是个傻子
The rest dismiss you as a pervert.
剩下的认为你是个龌龊下流之人
Am I mad to think I saw something in you?
是我疯了吗  我居然在你身上看到了些什么
Something of a man?
一个人们该有的品质
And just the sort Salem needs to fight the devil.
正是如今这恶魔横行的塞勒姆所需要的
Isaac, Isaac. Isaac, Isaac.
艾萨克  艾萨克
Oh, sweet Isaac.
亲爱的艾萨克
Abby?
艾比
Isaac.
艾萨克
How did you --
你怎么
Shh. My sweet.
嘘  亲爱的
Tell me --
告诉我
who was with you in the woods?
和你在森林里的人是谁
Who was what?
什么人
The other night.
那天晚上
Who was with you?
谁和你在一起
Who was with you, my sweet Isaac?
谁和你在一起  亲爱的艾萨克
Who was with you, my love?
谁和你在一起  亲爱的
No one can hear us.
没人会听到的
If you love me, you'll tell me.
如果你爱我就告诉我
I can't.
我不能
Tell me, and we'll be together again,
告诉我  我们就能又在一起了
just like we were.
像从前一样
I can't.
我不能
You can.
你可以的
You can't what?
你不能什么
You can. It's okay.
你可以的  没事的
Who was with you, my love?
谁和你在一起  亲爱的
It was John Alden.
是约翰·奥登
Good morning, magistrate.
早上好  治安官
Good morning, Mrs. Sibley.
早上好  西布里太太
What an unforeseen delight.
见到您真是意外之喜
Will you join me in some coffee?
要和我一起喝点咖啡吗
W-we've been experimenting with a new brazilian brew.
我们正在尝试一种新的巴西咖啡
May we speak?
能聊聊吗
The ladies are at prayer.
女士们在祷告
He was alone -- Isaac.
艾萨克当时是一个人
You questioned him? How?
你审问他了  怎么审的
He was alone in the woods.
他一个人在森林里
And that ends this persecution.
不必再为这事烦恼了
And you're absolutely certain
你能确信
that Isaac was telling the truth?
艾萨克说的是实话吗
The circumstances were such that a lie would not --
在那种情况下  他绝不会
could not -- cross his lips.
也不可能撒谎
Well, then, that leaves nothing
既然这样
but to task the selectmen to a vote
我们就只能让行政委员们投票
and hang the boy for witchcraft.
以巫师罪绞死那个孩子了
No.
不行
Salem will be no poorer for one less nitwit.
少一个蠢货塞勒姆也不会更悲惨
We will never truly know what he saw,
我们不知道他到底看见了多少
and what he saw could get us all killed.
他目击的一切可能会害死我们
I can control Isaac.
我能控制艾萨克
And what of the grand rite?
大祭典怎么办
You wanted another victim, and now you have one.
你需要另一个祭品  而现在就有一个
Tick-tock, mrs. Sibley.
时不我待  西布里太太
The next moon fast approaches.
下轮满月很快就到了
I will not let this happen.
我不会让你绞死他的
You're powerless to stop it.
你无能为力
The council will rule overwhelmingly against it.
委员会将全力反对
You will not do this!
你不能这么做
It can only be sentiment that's stopping you.
如今能阻止你的只有情感了
Such raw emotion.
这些猛烈的情感
It makes you vulnerable.
会成为你致命的弱点
Don't let it cloud your purpose.
别忘了你的初衷
He has to go.
他必须死
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里太太
Good morning, Anne.
早上好  安
They ain't mine.
这些不是我的
I've said it 10 ways from sunday!
从礼拜天起我已经用不同方式说过十遍了
Then how did they come to be on your person?
那它们怎么会在你身上
I don't know. The pigman must have put them on me.
我不知道  一定是猪头人放在我身上了
Or that blasted specter from the crags.
或是峭壁里那个可怕的怪物
The pigman?
猪头人
He saw us that night in the woods.
他那晚在林子里看到咱们了
That's why they're doing this to me.
所以他们才这么对我
Don't you see? They know I seen something.
你不明白吗  他们知道我看到了什么
What else do you remember?
你还记得些什么
- From the woods? - No.
-树林里的事吗  -不是
From the other night.
是另一个晚上
At -- at the rod
在...妓院
The whorehouse?
那个窑子吗
Nothing. I-I-I don't remember anything.
没有  我什么都不记得
I told you...
我告诉你了
Captain, a word.
上尉  借一步说话
Magistrate Hale will be here soon for Isaac.
霍尔治安官很快会回来找艾萨克
He's prepared to force a vote and hang him.
他准备强制投票来吊死他
You will stop him.
你必须阻止他
How?
怎么阻止
Any way you must.
不择手段
Well, the business of Salem awaits no man.
我得去处理塞勒姆的事务了
I know what you're doing, and I hate you for it.
我知道你要干什么  这让我深恶痛绝
Unacceptable language.
你这话简直是大不敬
Utterly and completely horrid sentiment.
这种冲动的情绪实在是太可怕了
My friend is dead.
我朋友才刚死
And you rush out to kill another.
你就急着去杀另一个
Darling, you must understand --
亲爱的  你必须明白
Even Mary Sibley,
就算是玛丽·西布里
with whom I share not a single common opinion,
一个我从未有过相同意见的人
finds your actions vile!
都觉得你的行为很低劣
And just how much of my conversation
你觉得你有什么资格
did you feel yourself entitled to?
能够和我谈这个
Enough to know that this persecution of Isaac is folly!
至少我知道这样迫害艾萨克简直是荒谬至极
Will you kill another, father?
你要再下毒手吗  父亲
Is that the "Business" you're so eager to attend to?
这就是你急着去处理的"事物"吗
Everything I do,
我所做的每一件事
I do for this family...
都是为了这个家
For its well-being
不光为它的安宁
and for the greater good of this town.
也是为了整个小镇
What?
怎么
No "How dare you?" or "Mind your elders"?
没有"你怎么敢"或是"注意尊长"吗
For once, my daughter, I agree with you.
这一次  我的女儿  我支持你
You do?
真的吗
But if I were you,
但如果我是你
I'd find an avenue around your distaste for Mrs. Sibley
我会抛开对西布里夫人的厌恶
in order to absorb her manners and ways.
以去学习她的手段和方法
She's despicable. I could never be like her.
她卑鄙无耻  我不可能成为她
She is a woman who has found her way to a voice.
她是一个拥有自己声音的女人
Look how she uses it.
看到她怎么运用了吗
You could use yours any way you like,
你也可以随意使用你的
but you have to find it first,
但你首先要找到它
unless you want to spend the rest of your life
除非你想花余生的时间
shouting at your father...
只对着你父亲大吼大叫
Or...your husband.
或者对你的丈夫
What did Mrs. Sibley require?
西布里夫人要干什么
Are you convinced of Isaac's innocence or guilt?
如今你相信艾萨克是无辜的还是有罪
I am not convinced of either.
我两种都不确定
Then stay the hell out of my way.
那就别插手
We shall take the boy to trial.
我们该带他去接受审判了
That path leads to the gallows.
那就等于将他送上了绞刑架
It's in no one man's hands.
这不是任何人可掌控的
Really? Whose hands is it in?
真的  那是谁掌控的
God's, of course.
当然是上帝了
No.
不
Need I remind you, son,
需要我提醒你吗  孩子
that you are impeding the very same man
你所阻挠之人在昨日
who only yesterday was your savior?
才刚救了你一命
Yeah. That was yesterday.
是啊  不过那是昨天了
You want Isaac today...
今天你要带艾萨克走
you got to go through me.
就必须通过我这关
The great John Alden disappears for a decade
伟大的约翰·奥登  消失了十年后
and then dares to come back
居然还胆敢回来
and dictate how to run our town?
并且插手我们小镇的事务
Take him.
逮捕他
He is not worth this Isaac.
为这个艾萨克这么做不值得
This has nothing to do with Isaac.
这和艾萨克无关
I know.
我知道
Which means it has to do with John Alden.
也就是说和约翰·奥登有关了
The magistrate will learn who leads us,
治安官将明白谁才是真正的领袖
and he will accept it.
而且他必须接受
Or?
不然呢
Help him.
帮帮他
Magistrate Hale, your daughter!
霍尔治安官  你的女儿
Stop! Get him back in the cell!
住手  把他关回牢里去
Stop! Stop!
住手  住手
Get him back in the cell!
把他弄回牢房去
What? What's happened?
怎么了  发生了什么
Has she eat something strange
她有没有服食任何花园里
-from the garden or the wood? -No.
-或树林中的奇怪东西  -没有
Was she bit by an insect or a critter?
她有没有被虫子或动物咬伤
No, no! Please!...
没有  快帮帮她
What's happened?
发生了什么
She -- she can't breathe!
她不能呼吸了
For god's sakes, man, do something!
看在上帝的份上  做点什么
She is beyond my arts.
我对此无能为力
Stop it!
住手
Make it stop!
求求你  住手吧
Magistrate, good afternoon.
治安官  下午好啊
I beg of you. Isaac can go free,
求求你  我会放了艾萨克
whatever you want. Just make it stop.
全听你的  求求你停手吧
- You will not question him. - No.
-不许再对他逼供  -不会了
You will get out of my way.
别再插手我的事
You will let me lead without further interference.
也不许再质疑我的权威
I will choose who lives and who dies.
我将决定谁生谁死
Yes, yes. Help her.
全听你的  救救她吧
You see, magistrate,
你要知道  治安官
I've lost everything in this town that I ever cared for.
在这个镇上我已经失去了值得牵挂的一切
You, however,
而你
You have everything left to lose --
你却有许多害怕失去的事物
a sentiment that makes you vulnerable.
这些情感正是你致命的弱点
Please.
求你了
My daughter.
放过我女儿
She's improved.
她情况好多了
I never understood it before --
以前我一直不明白
how my parents could send me away.
为什么父母忍心把我送走
What could be worse than being apart?
有什么会比与家人分离更残忍
Certainly not death.
肯定不是死亡
Now I know
如今我明白了
a parent will do anything for the life of their child.
父母会为了孩子的性命做出任何事情
What did you do?
你做了什么
What happened?
我是怎么了
It's all right, darling.
没事了  亲爱的
Everything's going to be all right.
一切都会好的
A confession --
说实话
I've thought, on occasion, my character might've been improved
有时我不禁会想  或许偶尔来一场殴斗
by the infrequent tussle.
会对我的性格有所帮助
Oh, yeah.
没错
Beating's done you a world of good.
你挨过的那些揍还真是让你获益良多
Why did you help me?
你为什么帮我
Even God demands a fair fight.
就算是上帝也需要一场公平的斗争
Gentlemen.
先生们
The selectmen and I feel, in this particular case,
行政委员和我一致认为  这件案子
that a trial and a vote will be unnecessary.
不需要进行审判与投票
Clearly, the lad was drunk.
显然  那小伙子只是喝醉了
We are willing to let him go and drop charges.
我们同意释放他  并撤销一切指控
Unless, of course, the reverend feels otherwise.
当然了  除非牧师不这么认为
A drunken romp is all --
就是一场醉酒闹事罢了
A young man's prerogative.
年轻人的特权
Why don't you tell him?
不如你去告诉他这个好消息吧
The good folks of Salem
塞勒姆的善良人民
have declared you a drunk and not a witch.
认为你只是喝醉了  而不是一个巫师
You're sprung.
你被释放了
I'm free?
我自由了
Yeah. Get the hell out of here.
没错  赶紧离开这鬼地方吧
Pretty sure no one's ever stood for me before.
从没有人为我说过话
Makes it hard to know what to say.
让我不知道该说什么好
You saved my life.
你救了我一命
Excellent news.
好消息
Isaac has been spared.
艾萨克被释放了
What? How?
怎么会
There simply wasn't the required evidence to convict.
因为没有足够的证据将他定罪
I told you I was thorough
我说过我一定会详细调查
And that the innocent...
所以只要你是无辜的
have no cause for alarm.
就根本无需担心
Does that not give you peace?
这还不足以消除你的忧虑吗
That is today,
这只是今天
but what of the days that follow?
但未来的日子呢
We will take them as they come.
无论发生什么  我们会一起面对
We will?
我们
I told you -- no harm will come to you.
我说过  我不会让你受到任何伤害
You can't be sure.
你没法保证
I can.
我可以
Do you ever wonder?
你是否曾想过
What?
什么
If we could leave this place?
或许我们可以离开这里
If we could forget Salem and its witches?
忘了塞勒姆和这些巫师们
If we could have a different life?
去过不同的生活
I believe I'm doing good.
我相信我做的一切都是正义的
I know.
我知道
And your father would be so very proud.
你的父亲一定会为你无比骄傲
Isaac has been freed?
艾萨克被释放了吗
Yes.
是的
Good.
那就好
You should see the militia.
你真该看看那些民兵的样子
I'm grateful.
我很感激
For Isaac.
你对艾萨克的帮助
Okay, then.
不用客气
John...
约翰
We were fortunate today,
今天我们只是幸运
but we might not be so lucky in days to come.
但好运不会一直伴随着我们
If you insist on staying...
如果你坚持留下
...you must understand I cannot protect you.
你必须明白  我将无法保护你